#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ahlam-khan-12925265 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Talent Management
English
Talent Acquisition

### Languages

English

# ahlam khan

Hiring for Artificial Intelligence/ Machine Learning, NLP experts and Data Scientists

Bengaluru

### Summary

Experienced Human Resources with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Human Resources, Talent Management, English, Microsoft Excel, and Performance Management. Strong human resources professional with a schooling focused in Mathematics from nirmal jyoti school.

### Experience

Accenture in India

HR

January 2016 - Present (4 years 8 months)

Bangalore

#### Accenture

HR

January 2016 - September 2017 (1 year 9 months)

bangalore

#### ONE DEGREE NORTH

**HR** Executive

September 2013 - January 2016 (2 years 5 months)

**BANGALORE** 

recruitment

### Rungta College of Engineering & Technology

1 year 1 month

lecturer

January 2012 - January 2013 (1 year 1 month)

lecturer

January 2012 - January 2013 (1 year 1 month)

## Education

nirmal jyoti school schooling, Mathematics · (2002 - 2005)